surveysite.com 2013-06-15

# Privacy Policy - comScore, Inc

comScore interacts with current and prospective clients, investors, and the general public via its Web site, comscore.com. This Privacy Statement describes comScore’s privacy-related policies and practices as they relate to the collection and use of information gathered from visitors to comscore.com. comScore operates a number of research panels, each of which are governed by the privacy policy that appears on the Web site assigned to that research panel.

**Privacy Commitment**  
Privacy is a critical issue to every Internet user and comScore is committed to assuring that the privacy and confidentiality of visitors to this site are respected and preserved. Unless you give us explicit permission, we will not share your personally identifiable information such as name, address or e-mail address with third parties for any purpose. Information gathered from your activity is used for compiling anonymous statistics only and is not identifiable back to any individual. Registration information is used for verification purposes, for sending administrative e-mails to clients regarding our service, and for sending informational e-mails to prospective clients, investors, and the general public, if requested.

**Collection, Use, Disclosure of Information**  
 comScore does not collect personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide us personally identifiable information through an online form or e-mail communication or you are accessing client-specific, secure content. We use cookies to ensure authorized access to client-specific secure content. Our use of cookies is explained in greater detail below. When accessing client-specific secure content, you are acting as a representative of your company and your interactions with our site in this capacity are governed by our relationship agreement with your company.

Our site also automatically creates logs regarding your and other user sessions on comscore.com, such as features that you use, the actions that you take, and the information that you access. We generally use this information in statistical and aggregate formats to assess the effectiveness of our site and to better understand your priorities and interests.

comScore does not sell, distribute or disclose your personally identifiable information collected from comscore.com to third parties without your consent. However, we may release information to a third party if required by a legal process such as a subpoena or a search warrant, in which case we will notify you of the disclosure.Please note that visitors to comscore.com are not required to provide us personally identifiable information to use the public areas of our site. You can provide us information such as address, e-mail address, or telephone number if you would like to learn more about comScore’ products and services. Data submitted to comscore.com by current and prospective clients, investors, and the general public will be purged in a reasonable period of time after the parties have stopped communicating with us or have requested removal.

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of data stored on a user’s hard drive that contain information about a user. In the case of secure content access, if your company is a client of comScore, we use a cookie that contains your login information, so we can ensure that client-specific information is secure from unauthorized access. We utilize an encrypted cookie to track client access to client-specific secure content. These cookies are used only for this purpose and are intended to be used only by our Web site. Please note that you can view and delete these cookies using the features of your browser.

**Choice and Data Access**  
As a representative of your company, you can view and modify your company profile information in the secure client area of our site.

**Data Security/Integrity**  
comScore has physical, electronic, and managerial security functions in place to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. Only authorized employees have access to the data you provided and that access is limited by need. Our employees who have access to the data you provided have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information.

**European Data**  
For personal information that comScore receives from the European Economic Area, comScore has committed to handling such personal information in accordance with the Safe Harbor Principles and the 15 FAQs. comScore’s Safe Harbor certification can be found at <http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list>. For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Website at <http://export.gov/safeharbor/>.

**Children**  
comScore understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the online interactive world. This Web site does not intentionally target or solicit to children 13 and younger.

**Notification of Changes**  
 If we materially change our practices in handling personally identifiable information, as described in this statement, we will notify you by posting the changes on this Privacy Statement at least 30 days prior to their implementation.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement as it relates to your use of this site or comScore’ products and services, please submit a privacy inquiry.
